[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Americas first continuously-published newspaper?", "correct_answer": "Boston News-Letter", "incorrect_answers": ["Boston Globe", "Boston Star", "Boston Herald"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Benjamin Green invent in 1944?", "correct_answer": "Coppertone", "incorrect_answers": ["Kevlar", "The garage door opener.", "TiVo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other interesting name is commonly used for the Chinese meal fo tiao qiang, also known as Consummation of Happiness and Longevity?", "correct_answer": "Buddha Jumps Over the Wall", "incorrect_answers": ["A Geisha Sings Under The Blossoming Peach", "The Murder Of The Samurai", "The Son Of The Emperor Is Born"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wendy Beamish, a character from St. Elmos Fire, worked as a welfare counselor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tomato Frogs tend to hit sexual maturity in about 9-14 months.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first draft of Alien 3 is the one that was filmed.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year were the first Moa remains discovered by Europeans?", "correct_answer": "1839", "incorrect_answers": ["1765", "1857", "1724"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2001 Japanese animated movie Spirited Away is about  Chichiro and her parents being trapped in what seems to be a deserted amusement park.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who/what is the title character in the 2006 movie Eragon?", "correct_answer": "A Boy", "incorrect_answers": ["A City", "A Warrior", "A Dragon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the horror movie Dawn of the Dead, the goal of the lead characters is to destroy the undead before the disease spreads any further", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1973 Spanish horror film stars Christopher Lee, Peter Cushing and Telly Savalas.", "correct_answer": "Horror Express", "incorrect_answers": ["City of the Dead", "Hanging Woman", "The Creeping Flesh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the first loaf of sliced bread sold?", "correct_answer": "July 7, 1928", "incorrect_answers": ["March 29, 1925", "June 17, 1921", "September 21, 1916"]}]